Bok!
What's this? Did you kidnap her?
She attacked me last night.
Someone has to do it, Bok.
Is it why Carlota's here?
It's because you want
somebody to watch over me?
Why did you release her?
You let go of La Fornarina.
She is not La Fornarina.
La Fornarina is left-handed.
These drivers are always
delayed in deliveries.
There is no sign of reprimand.
Why is that?
I need to report this to Agent Alex.
They said I shouldn't use this phone.
I need to listen to Agent Alex.
You really love leading people on, Mikoy.
Such a heartbreaker.
Who was the one you sent that messed up?
Chihuahua.
and now he is even more exposed.
And maybe you're forgetting something.
Norberto.
For La Morte Bianca.
So you focus on that
and let me handle this.
What's the agent's name?
I'll play your game,
but as soon as I finish with my mission,
you will give me all the information
about the agent getting close to Mikoy,
and I'll deal with that bastard next.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes, sir, I'm fine.
Just a stomach bug.
Good thing Agent Sianong was there.
He always carries medicine.
Sir, we have a problem.
The sensors at the back were triggered!
Someone's breaking into the secret door!
Kian, secure General Norberto.
Let's go, sir.
Hold on a second!
Stop it!
Who do you think I am?
A civilian who needs protection?
I can fight.
Team, let's go.
Go.
Hands up! Or we'll shoot--
Mikoy?
Hmm?
Really? Laurence is your date
for the concert?
Why? Is that bad?
No, I am just surprised.
Luisa Mae said
that you were coming with us.
She also said that
you were bringing your boyfriend, so…
You mean,
you and Laurence are…?
Okay.
Let's just say that
we're still in the getting-to-know stage.
But there's no label yet.
Oh, right.
You're not really into labels.
Why? Is that bad?
No.
I did not mean to insult you.
You didn't mean to, but you already did.
I'm sorry.
Okay, how about this?
Once we get to the concert,
I'll give you and Laurence some space
so the two of you can
get closer to each other.
And…
I'm also planning to propose to Luisa Mae.
Propose what?
Propose!
To formalize our relationship!
So we can officially
become boyfriend and girlfriend.
So finally,
we'll have a label for each other.
Right?
Lower your gun.
Sianong, lower your gun.
You first.
What are you doing, huh?
Do you even know
you almost got yourself shot?
And what are you doing
at our secret door, like an agent?
How did you know about that?
I'm the one who told him about it.
I told him to use that entrance,
so our enemies wouldn't discover
the identity of our secret asset.
That's it, just like what Alex said.
Secret door for the…
secret asset.
But, Mikoy, what are you doing here?
I specifically instructed you
to wait for our instructions,
to wait for us to contact you.
Didn't you understand what I said?
Because I missed you.
Okay?
I miss your eyes…
your voice…
your touch,
everything.
I really missed you.
Why?
Do you feel the same way about me?
Just kidding! Come on!
Are you okay?
You're way too tense.
Loosen up a little. Come on.
You know, you had too much coffee.
One day, I'm really gonna get you.
Come on. I was kidding.
You can't even take a joke.
I really did miss you, guys.
What are you even doing here?
I'm here because I have
new information you need to know.
So tasty!
Thank you.
By the way, why were you all
so worked up earlier?
You had too much coffee, didn't you?
That's why you don't want coffee now?
And we think the Moravianos
are trying to kill our agency director.
Sir… Norberto Ruiz?
Yes.
A lot has happened these past few days,
and the Moravianos
already know everything we're doing.
And another thing.
We're already on their radar.
They even sent La Fornarina
just to silence Alex.
It's nothing.
No, it's not.
It's not just nothing.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm a special agent.
I can handle it. You know me.
Even if you can handle it,
even if you're used to it,
it still affects you, right?
Maybe not physically,
but spiritually,
mentally,
emotionally.
- Mikoy.
- Alex!
Look at me.
I want to know.
Are you really okay?
What is the meaning of this?
Oh…
Who is this new face?
Who is this?
Your new boyfriend?
Another pretty boy actor wannabe.
Is he a new member of Starworx of Mr. M?
What if I really am her boyfriend?
Why?
Got a problem with that?
See?
We're not human. We're not animals.
We're a thing.
Bro! Is it true that you and Sofie…
Why? Is it that unbelievable?
Not really.
I just thought you weren't Sofie's type.
Maybe I just misunderstood her.
If you know her that well,
do you know,
or did you at least ask,
what she thinks about Luisa Mae?
Did you ask her permission
about Luisa Mae?
Permission?
Why would I ask permission?
She already knows
how much I like Luisa Mae.
She was actually the first one
who became friends with Luisa.
And after that,
Luisa and I started talking.
Wait, why are you asking anyway?
Oh, Angelito!
That sigh was a bit too much, bro.
Have you heard about the theory of us men
who tend to develop emotionally
a bit later?
Meaning, we mature late.
You mean,
we're late bloomers?
Exactly.
We're late bloomers
when it comes to relationships.
I don't believe that, bro.
Come on. Tell me.
You already had a girlfriend in Grade 5.
We're quick when it comes to girlfriends,
but it doesn't mean we're already
mature enough for relationships.
Wait.
What's this philosophical discourse for?
So you really don't get it?
You know the snake's about to bite you.
It's so obvious.
It's right in front of you.
Huh?
You know what? Whatever.
I'm heading inside.
Take care.
We do have a love team, right?
MikLex.
Mikoy and Alex.
MikLex, my ass.
So corny!
You and Lai… still look better together.
- Lai?
- Lai…
Laida Magtalas.
But wait.
You do look familiar.
I think I've seen you before.
Well…
as the Bisdak Heartthrob of Cebu City,
people really have mistaken me
for an actor before.
Sometimes even the King of Gil,
who's haggard.
I got it!
You look exactly like this idiot I know,
Gabo Villarica.
The one who ghosted
my friend Belinda Dimagiba.
Huh?
Where did that come from?
From me!
Are you deaf?
Oh, no, Alex,
you better be careful with him.
You're both ghosts.
He might leave you too
without saying goodbye.
Just like what you did to me.
That's enough.
It's Mikoy.
You saw him at the hospital.
The one who got shot
at the Valtrovi event.
He's working for us.
He's our asset.
I know.
I was just messing with him.
But this is a surprise, huh?
Who would've thought
the dumb victim from the Valtrovi event
is actually the asset of this agency?
Hey, watch it!
Don't judge me. I'm not a book.
And wow, thanks for calling me dumb.
Why? Can't you take a bullet
for the one you love?
I'm just saying that
if you are an important asset,
you should learn how to protect yourself
to not get shot.
I already know how! I've been training!
You wanna go 1-on-1?
Enough already.
Mikoy, tell us about
the fresh information you mentioned.
That's why you're here.
Oh, right!
You distracted me with coffee,
and this guy's being extra.
I almost forgot.
Anyway, I'm here
because I brought fresh information.
But I have even fresher information.
Did you know
that some turtles
can breathe through their butts?
Really, Ben?
You know, this is why you're always…
no, not just always…
You're constantly out of pocket!
Can you read the room?
That's why you often get ghosted.
Is that victim blaming?
Are you spying on turtles now?
Stop it! Wait a minute!
I might forget
the fresh information again.
Anyway…
There. You see that?
These are all the files
of Vertex's drivers.
Nice.
Anyway,
I'm here because I want to say
I think I've cracked down
on the Moravianos' local operation.
I think I know how to bring them down.
I noticed that there
are four Vertex drivers
who are always late
for their delivery schedules at the port.
Every M, W, F.
Over and over again.
And these drivers,
not a single one has a report with HR.
No suspension, no penalty.
Looks like they have strong connections.
Not just strong connections.
More like a direct line to heaven.
Something fishy.
But I think this is the breakthrough
that we need for this case.
Good job.
You're right, Sianong.
Thank you, Mikoy, for the intel.
Who would've thought?
Peace offering.
One for each of us.
Yes, Angelito and I are cool now!
If you know her that well,
do you know,
or did you at least ask,
what's her opinion about Luisa Mae?
Did you ask permission about Luisa Mae?
Why isn't Sofie replying?
Sofie, please answer me.
Hey, you called?
Well, I just thought about Sofie.
Are you still together?
Didn't you have
the same last subject earlier?
Yes, but after class,
I went to the library.
So you're still at the library now?
No, I had somewhere to go.
Why? Why are you looking for her?
Um…
I wanted to ask her out to eat.
She usually gets night cravings
around this time.
But all right.
Bro, if you see her, just tell her
that my room's open for hangout again.
I don't think
we'll be seeing each other, bro.
Because earlier,
when class ended, she left in a hurry.
So maybe she's getting her beauty rest.
Yes, that makes sense.
Why?
Do you miss her?
Yes.
I kinda miss that idiot annoying me.
She was always bothering me.
So now I can really feel
that her presence is missing.
But all right, bro, thanks.
All right, bye.
Just hearing that someone misses you,
and you're already giggling.
I'm not giggling, okay?
Yes, that's true.
If you're just friends,
then why are you avoiding him?
You like him, don't you?
Or is it one-sided love?
And you know what?
A one-sided crush is better anyway.
So why are you avoiding him?
Because I can't take it anymore!
It's always Luisa, Luisa, Luisa!
You know, when I sleep,
I even dream about Luisa now.
I know so much about Luisa already,
it feels like I'm the one who likes her
because of your friend's stories.
So that's it then?
You're giving up?
Just because he's talking about Luisa Mae?
Maybe.
How can you give up so easily
when the fight hasn't even started yet?
But haven't I already lost?
Angelito likes Luisa.
Don't give up just because
he likes someone else.
Be honest with your intentions
and let him know
that you and your feelings exist.
Fight for your feelings.
You know what? You're right.
The fight is just getting started.
I can do this.
Are you okay?
Well, I'm still alive.
I just need to get out of here.
I can't go to the hospital.
- Come on. Come with me.
- People will notice.
Son of a…
You're still alive?
They say…
I'm like a cat.
I have nine lives.
Sweetheart?
Are you there?
Sweetheart.
And why should I trust you?
I don't need your trust.
All you have to do is listen.